Guide to the James E. Dyer Papers MS 052
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Series III: Political and Professional Career, RG6.xx___x
  - Subseries D: Politcal Career, RG6.xx___x
    - Connecticut General Assembly Legislative Committee Directory, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Connecticut General Assembly Legislative Record Index, Final Edition, 1977 (Box 88)
    - Connecticut General Assembly Legislative Record Index, 1977 (Box 88)
    - Connecticut Young Democrats, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence (ALS William A. O'Neill,Christopher J. Dodd), 1977 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Democrats, 1977-1979 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Equitable Tax Association, 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 12-14)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Grasso Campaign (correspondence), 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Jefferson-Jackson Dinner Programs, 1977-1985 (Box 44, Folder 18-21)
    - Memorabilia (local and state), 1977 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Press Releases, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Resolutions,Official Citations, Certificates of Appreciation, Proclamation, 1977-1987 (Box OS 3)
    - Roads/Transportation, 1977-1982 (Box 43, Folder 15-16)
    - Sample Ballot, 1977 Election (Box OS 13)
    - Speeches, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Speeches (Graduation, Youth-Politics), 1977-1987 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Speeches (Graduation), 1977-1987 (Box 45, Folder 3-6)
    - State House of Representatives IDs, 1977-1980 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - "Welcome James Dyer State Representative 110th District" Poster used at Danbury Fair 1977-1979 on Danbury Day (14x22 poster) (Box OS 13)
    - Bernard, Alfred J. (clippings and notes), 1978 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Campaign Ads, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Campaign Clippings, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 10-12)
    - Campaign Correspondence (Congratulatory letters from local/state officials), 1978 (Box 45, Folder 13-14)
    - Campaign Debate, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Campaign Form Letters (includes WCSC 6/78 graduation list), 1978 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Campaign Mailing List, Danbury High School, 1978-1979 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Campaign Mailing List, General, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 1-3)
    - Campaign Memorabilia (pins, flyers, bumper stickers, photograph, etc.), 1978 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Campaign Novelty Items (catalogs), 1978 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Campaign Organizational Information, 1978 (Box OS 5)
    - Campaign Organizational Information, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Campaign Press Releases, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Campaign Questionnaires, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Campaign Kick-Off, September 20, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Campaign Election Victory, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Connecticut General Assembly Legislative Record Index, Final Edition, 1978 (Box 88)
    - Connecticut General Assembly Legislative Record Index, 1978 (Box 88)
    - Correspondence (ALS Chris Dodd and William Ratchford), 1978 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - ELLA, She Makes the Difference. Elect Ella Grasso. Vote Democratic, Poster and Campaign Miscellany, 1978 (Box OS 5)
    - Lawmaking in Connecticut: The General Assembly, Wayne R. Swanson, 1978 (Box 90)
    - Connecticut General Assembly Legislative Record Index, Final Edition, 1978 (Box 88)
    - Organizational Information '78 (sample voting machine ballot), 1978 (Box OS 5)
    - Outstanding Young Men of America Certificates, 1978-1983 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Platform Committee, State Democratic Convention, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 12-14)
    - Speeches: Business Woman's Professional Club Speech, 1978-1979 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - State Democratic Convention, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 16-17)
    - Budget, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Campaign '79 ADS, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Campaign '79 Miscellany, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Common Council, December 1979 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Common Council Meetings and Special Meetings, Minutes (December 4,1979 to December 1, 1981), 1979-1981 (Box 47, Folder 4-13)
    - Conference/Task Force, 1979-1980 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence C-79 (incoming) ALS Christopher J. Dodd, Ella Grasso, Joe Lieberman, Abe Ribicoff, and other local/state officials, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 4-11)
    - Correspondence, General (incoming/outgoing), 1979 (Box 48, Folder 12-13)
    - Correspondence (incoming), 1979-1980 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Danbury Fair Mall Correspondence, 1979-1985 (Box 48, Folder 15-17)
    - Danbury Fair Mall "Original Design to Eliminate Traffic Hazard" (aerial view), 1979-1985 (Box OS 11)
    - Danbury Redevelopment Agency: Planning Department, Staff Reports and Review of Targeted Projects, 1979-1987 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Danbury Redevelopment Agency: Steinberg (Robert M.) Files, 1979-1982 (Box 49, Folder 1-3)
    - Debate #1 9/15/1979, Terry vs. Dyer (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Democrats 110th District (ALS Ella Grasso, Toby Moffett), 1979 (Box 49, Folder 5-7)
    - Distinguished Service Award from the Danbury Jaycees (plaque), 1979 (Box 96)
    - Early Planning Lists and Schedules, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Guest Books for Oath of Office, 1979-1981 (Box 90)
    - Inauguration Speech '79, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Information from Danbury News-Times,June 10, 1979 to Present [March 31, 1980], James E. Dyer (Student Paper), 1979-1980 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Information: from announcement to Mayor to NYU Class, 1979-1990 (Box 49, Folder 9-12)
    - Jaycee's Award Correspondence (ASL Lowell Weicker, Ella Grasso, Abe Ribicoff, Joseph Lieberman, Toby Moffett), 1979 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Jaycee's Award Guest Book, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Legislature Years, 1979-1985 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Legislature 1979-80 / Liason Information, 1979-1982 (Box 50, Folder 4-5)
    - Mailing Lists--JD '79, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Mailings--JD '79 Volunteers, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Mailings, WCSC List to 3/12/79, 1979 (Box OS 5)
    - Management/Organization Lecture, 1979-1980 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Mayor '79 Organizational File, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Name Plate from Council Chamber, Mayor's podium 11/79 to 11/85 (inscribed on back), 1979-1985 (Box 92)
    - Oath of Office Certificates, Invitations, Programs, 1979-1983 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Parking Authority, 1979-1985 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Personnel Notes and Biographies (CLOSED), 1979-1984 (Box 51, Folder 1-2)
    - Planning Department Reorganization, 1979-1981 (Box 51, Folder 3-6)
    - Press Releases (as State Representative), 1979 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Press Releases (as Mayor), 1979 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Print Ads, 1979-1987 (Box OS 12)
    - Questionnaire, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Session 1979 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Speech, Henry Abbott Tech, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Speech, Rotary Club, September 2, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - State of Connecticut House Joint Resolution No. 201 (framed), 1979 (Box OS 2)
    - Telegram from Ella Grasso, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Tricentennial Committee, 1979-1984 (Box 51, Folder 11-13)
    - White House Youth Employment Initiatives, January 10, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Young Democratic Club of Connecticut, Inc., 6th Annual Convention Booklet, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - To Mayor Jim Dyer, With Loving Thanks….Our 2nd Annual Black White + Free Gospel Concert (Plaque), 1980 (Box 96)
    - Boy Scouts of America, Cub Scouts, Mayor James Dyer, With Many Thanks 2-29-80 (Plaque), 1980 (Box 96)
    - Boy Scouts of America, Certificate of Appreciation for supporting Blue & Gold dinner, Pack 9, 3/26/1980 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Budget Speech (First), 1980 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Budget Notes, 1980-1981 (Box 50, Folder 13-14)
    - Carter-Mondale Re-election, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Census Data, 1980-1981 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - City Progress & Budget Laws 9/30/1980 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Common Council Meeting 1/80, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Common Council Agenda and Minutes, 2/5/1980 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Common Council Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 56, Folder 2-3)
    - Correspondence, General (mainly outgoing), 1980 (Box 52, Folder 1-3)
    - Correspondence, General (incoming/outgoing), 1980 (Box 52, Folder 4-9)
    - Correspondence (Miscellaneous), 1980-1981 (Box 52, Folder 10-13)
    - Correspondence (incoming) ALS Wm.O'Neill, E.Grasso, Wm.Ratchford, R.Blumenthal, T.Moffett, C.Dodd, 1980-1982 (Box 52, Folder 14-17)
    - Correspondence (incoming) ALS Wm.O'Neill, E.Grasso, Wm.Ratchford, R.Blumenthal, T.Moffett, C.Dodd, 1980-1982 (Box 53, Folder 1-4)
    - Danbury Downtown Council, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 5-8)
    - Danbury Downtown Council By-Laws, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Danbury Fair Mall, 1980-1986 (Box 56, Folder 5-6)
    - Danbury Fair Mall Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Danbury Fair Mall/Route 7, 1980-1985 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Danbury Fair Ground Breaking July 11, 1984, and Danbury Green Redevelopment Project Ground Breaking July 16, 1986 (shovel), 1980-1994 (Item 4)
    - Danbury Fair "Sight Seeing Ride" Circular Sign, ca.1980 (Box OS 12)
    - Danbury History/Facts Clippings, 1980-2000 (Box 56, Folder 7-8)
    - Danbury Planning Department, 1980-1987 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Danbury State Fair, Danbury Day Ribbon, 1980 (Box OS 3)
    - Danbury Redevelopment Agency: Steinberg--Excerpted Redevelopment Documents, 1980-1982 (Box 53, Folder 11-12)
    - Danbury Redevelopment Agency: Robert M. Steinberg, 1980-1987 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Danbury Redevelopment Project, Overall Information, 1980-1987 (Box 53, Folder 14-17)
    - "The Democratic Town Committee of Danbury Presents A Review "Happy Days Are Here Again II" June 7, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - The Democrats, 1980 Democratic National Convention (Booklet) (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Dodd Advisory Committee (ALS by Chris Dodd), 1980-1981 (Box 54, Folder 1-2)
    - Housatonic Valley Council of Elected Officials Declaration of Appreciation Awarded to James E. Dyer, For Eight Years of Distinguished Service (Plaque), ca.1980 (Box 96)
    - International Association of Lions Clubs, Certificate of Membership, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Issues - Affirmative Action, 1980-1986 (Box 54, Folder 4-8)
    - Issues - Housing, 1980-1987 (Box 54, Folder 5-16)
    - Landfill and City vs. Galante, 1980-1981 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Landfill, Robert M. Steinberg, 1980-1982 (Box 56, Folder 10-11)
    - Mass Mailings, 1980-1983 (Box 55, Folder 2-5)
    - Mayor's Conference on Historic Preservation, May 16, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 6-7)
    - Mayor's Conference on Housing, June 12-13,1980 (Box 56, Folder 11-12)
    - Mayor's Conference on Women and Family, Oct. 6-7, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Mayor's Policy Statement on Land Use and Development, Tri-State Town Meeting, 6/19/80 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Paul Garavel, 110th, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Paul Garavel, State Representative (glass dish), ca.1980 (Box 95)
    - Press Releases, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Proclamations (copies), 1980 (Box 55, Folder 12-14)
    - STOP THE DRAFT. Washington March 22, poster (17x24), 1980 (Box OS 12)
    - "Superhawk" poster (Ronald Reagan), 1980 (Box OS 13)
    - Ted Kennedy for President, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Thanks for not smoking (sign from Mayor's desk, clear acrylic with yellow lettering), 1980 (Box 94)
    - Valentine's Day Dance Card, White House Pass, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - White House Youth Education and Employment Initiative, January 10, 1980 (Includes 1981 Federal Budget Information) (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Youth Issues, 1980-1981 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Budget, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Budget Speech, 1981-1982 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Campaign Open 10/25/81, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Campaign 1981 (Box 58, Folder 4-6)
    - Campaign Briefing Booklet, 1981-1982 (Box 57, Folder 1-6)
    - Case Work (Jeff/Eric), 1981 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - City limits by Paul E. Peterson, 1981 (Box 90)
    - Clippings, 1981-1982 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - "Continued Progress with a Positive Team; Jim Dyer, Mayor…." (21x43 sign), 1981 (Item 36)
    - Correspondence (incoming) ALS W. Ratchford, Stephen Feldman, Chris Dodd, Joe Lieberman, 1981 (Box 57, Folder 8-12)
    - Correspondence, General (incoming/outgoing), 1981 (Box 57, Folder 13-14)
    - Correspondence (planning & zoning, sewers, traffic, Wilmorite, lakefront development, and redevelopment), 1981-1987 (Box 57, Folder 15-16)
    - Correspondence (City Litigation), 1981-1984 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Danbury Fair Train Sign (Last used 1981) (Box OS 12)
    - Davis+Geck Ad, 1981 (Box OS 12)
    - Debate, 1981 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - E. T. (Eugene F. Tomanio), 1981-1985 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - For Deposit Only, Jim Dyer - 81 Committee, Thomas J.Dyer, Treasurer (rubber stamp), 1981 (Box 94)
    - Form Letters, 1981 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Grace 'N Vessels of Christ Thank You Mayor James Dyer For Again Supporting Us At The Black White And Free Hallelujah Parade (plaque), 1981 (Box 96)
    - Intern Thank You Notes, 1981-1986 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Issues - Downtown (Task Force), 1981-1984 (Box 58, Folder 10-13)
    - Issues - Education Information, 1981-1987 (Box 59, Folder 1-3)
    - Kenosia Pipeline Clipping, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous notes, reports and clippings, 1981-1990 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - NASA: Space Shuttle Launches, Information Summaries of Major NASA Launches, Landsat 1,2& 3 Coverage Index, NASA Astronauts, Hubble Space Telescope, 1981-1994 (Box 59, Folder 6-13)
    - NASA: Space Shuttle Launches and Astronauts and Landsat 1,2,3 Coverage Index for 1983-1984, 1981-1994 (Box OS 12)
    - The News-Times, Dyer sees himself bridging old, new (metal poster 22x14), 1981 (Box OS 13)
    - The News-Times, Dyer Crushes GOP, November 4, 1981, pages 1-12 (Box OS 9)
    - The News-Times, The Great Danbury State Fair, A Commemorative Edition, Friday, October 2, 1981 (newspaper supplement (Box OS 9)
    - Partnership, Investment & Opportunity, Danbury White Paper by JD, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Planning (Debate material and planning '81 campaign), 1981 (Box OS 12)
    - Planning (Debate material and planning '81 campaign), 1981 (Box 58, Folder 14-15)
    - Press Releases, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 15-17)
    - Print Ads, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Proclamations (originals), 1981 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Proclamations (copies), 1981 (Box 60, Folder 1-3)
    - Public Utilities, Water (includes one 5x7 b/w photograph dated March 2, 1982), 1981-1982 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Recipes from Danbury (sister city in England), 1981 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Setaro, Jr., Dominic A., 1981-1989 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook on Political Election by Patty Burke (clippings), 1981 (Box OS 4)
    - Mayor Dyer Survey Project, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 2-3)
    - Mayor Dyer Survey Overall Project Results, 1981 (Box OS 9)
    - Water Supply Project (Includes Report to The City of Danbury on Proposed Improvements to Water Supply by Hazen & Whipple, Civil Engineers, 1926), 1981-1982 (Box 62, Folder 4-6)
    - World, Union Carbide Newsletters, May/June 1981 and December 1981 (Box OS 3)
    - Budget Notes, 1982-1983 (Box 62, Folder 7-8)
    - Budget Speech, 1982-1983 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Case Work, ca.1982 (Box 87)
    - Case Work Completed, JD, 1982-1984 (Box 60, Folder 6-8)
    - Certificates of Appreciation (Roberts Avenue Elementary School, The Greater Danbury Board of Realtors,Danbury Regional Commission on Child Care, Rights, and Abuse, Inc., and The American Cancer Society), 1982-1986 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Commissions, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Connecticut Business Review, August 1982 (Box OS 10)
    - Correspondence (mainly thank you letters from local constituents), 1982 (Box 60, Folder 11-15)
    - Correspondence (thank you letters from children attending Danbury schools), 1982-1986 (Box 97)
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 16-18)
    - Exchange Club of Danbury Conn., Veterans Day, 1982 (Box 96)
    - The Great Danbury State Fair Auction Catalog, March 31 through April 5, 1982 (Box OS 9)
    - Housing, Executive Summary, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Issues - KKK (incoming correspondence), 1982-1984 (Box 61, Folder 1-5)
    - Issues - KKK, The Klansman, issue 77, June 1982, 1982-1984 (Box OS 12)
    - Issues - Water Supply, Remarks of Mayor James E. Dyer, Monday, March 29, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Letters of Recommendations, 1982-1986 (Box 61, Folder 7-8)
    - NASA Landing of Space Shuttle Columbia STS-5, November 16, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 10-11)
    - Press Releases, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 9-10)
    - Proclamations (originals), 1982 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Proclamations (copies), 1982 (Box 61, Folder 12-14)
    - Proclamation Schedules, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 12-16)
    - Berol Gold and Silver Club, Honorary Member (framed), 1983 (Box 96)
    - Budget, 1983-1984 (Box OS 9)
    - Budget, 1983-1984 (Box 63, Folder 1-2)
    - Cabinet Meetings, 1983-1987 (Box 63, Folder 3-4)
    - Case Work (Anthony Coppolla, Peter Glaser, Evonne Norgado/Internal), 1983-1985 (Box 61, Folder 15-19)
    - Case Work (Anthony Coppolla, Peter Glaser, Evonne Norgado/Internal), 1983-1985 (Box 64, Folder 1-4)
    - Centennial Edition Volume I 1883-1933. The News-Times, September 8, 1983 (Box OS 9)
    - Centennial Edition Volume I, Part Two. The News-Times, September 8, 1983 (Box OS 9)
    - Centennial Edition Volume II, 1933-1983. The News Times, September 22, 1983 (Box OS 9)
    - Centennial Edition Volume II, 1933-1983. Part Two, The News Times, September 22, 1983 (Box OS 9)
    - Commissions, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (mainly congratulatory letters and notes from local/state officials and constituents) ALS Lowell Weicker, Toby Moffett, William Ratchford; Edward Koch, Mayor New York City and Carol Bellamy, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 6-16)
    - Correspondence, General, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 1-5)
    - DANBURY; Three Hundred Years of Change and Growth by Truman Warner (Signed by T.Clark Hull,Steve Collins,Gertrude Braun,Imogene Heireth,BEC?) 2 copies, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - DATAHR, The First Annual Dinner, June 20, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Democratic Delicacies 1983 (cookbook) (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Desk Set: James E. Dyer, Mayor with two Cross pens, 1983 (Box 95)
    - Issues - Infrastructure, 1983-1985 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Issues - Infrastructure, 1983 Public Improvement Bond Issue dated August 6, 1984, 1983-1984 (Box OS 12)
    - Issues - State Lobbying--Roads, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Issues - Jobs Outlook, 1983-1988 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Main Street Historic District, National Register of Historic Places, November 29, 1983, Certificate (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Mayoral Security, 1983-1987 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Media - Live, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Mondale/Ferraro Election Miscellany (ALS Walter Mondale), 1983 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Morgado, Evonne, Intern (Correspondence w/WVU Professors), 1983 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Organizational Chart, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Press Releases, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Proclamations (copies), 1983 (Box 63, Folder 6-8)
    - Re-election Campaign (correspondence and notes), 1983 (Box 63, Folder 9-10)
    - Testimonial to Most Reverend Walter W. Curtis, S.T.D., Bishop of the Diocese of Bridgeport, May 19, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Academic Excellence, 1984-1986 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Budget Notes, 1984-1985 (Box 63, Folder 11-12)
    - Campaign Material, 1984 (Box OS 12)
    - City of Danbury Commemorating Three Hundred Years of Progress (paperweight), 1984 (Box 94)
    - Commissions, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Common Council Meeting Agenda, February 1984 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence (ALS Chris Dodd, William Ratchford, Gov.William O'Neill), 1984 (Box 67, Folder 3-11)
    - Correspondence, General, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 12-17)
    - Danbury Fair Press Kit, 1984 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Danbury Redevelopment Agency: Larsen, Durgy & Co., 1984 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Danbury Redevelopment Agency: Eugene P. Barrett, 1984-1985 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Danbury Redevelopment, Errichetti Decision, 1984-1987 (Box 63, Folder 15-18)
    - Danbury Tricentennial Pursuit (board game), 1984-1985 (Box OS 8)
    - Deinstitutionalization, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Historice Preservation Handbook; A Guide To Preservation in Danbury (Booklet), 1984 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Hollings, The Thinking Man's Dark Horse for '84 by the Hollings for President Committee, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Issues - Bonding, 1984-1985 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Issues - C. D. Parks Property (Tarrywile), 1984-1986 (Box 68, Folder 6-8)
    - Issues - Crime, 1984-1986 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Issues - Democratic Town Committee (Danbury 2000), 1984-1986 (Box 66, Folder 2-3)
    - Issues - Elderly, 1984-1987 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Issues - Legislative Program, 1984-1985 (Box 68, Folder 11-12)
    - Issues - Moratorium/Growth Speech 6/84, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Issues - Recreation Speech Notes, 1984-1985 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Issues - Small Business, 1984-1985 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Ives Gala, June 9, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Mill Plain Road, Site of Westwood Village (Includes Traffic/Land Use, Management Study ), 1984 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Lake Place Condominiums - Piece of trolley track, 1984 (Item 1)
      Plaque reads Specimen of Danbury-Bethel trolley track circa 1895 uncovered during sewer line excavation for Lake Place Condominiums, Kenosia Avenue, Danbury, Connecticut October, 1984
    - Parking Authority Investigation, 1984-1985 (Box 68, Folder 16-17)
    - Press Releases, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Proclamations (copies), 1984 (Box 66, Folder 6-8)
    - State/Local Action Conference, February 25, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Tricentennial Proclamation (original), 1984 (Box OS 3)
    - Tricentennial, 1984-1985 (Box 66, Folder 9-10)
    - Tricentennial Celebration, 1984-1985 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Tricentennial Belt Buckle, 1984 (Box OS 7)
    - Tricentennial Flag (4x6), 1984-1985 (Box OS 7)
    - Tricentennial Guest Name Tag, 1984-1985 (Box OS 7)
    - Tricentennial Insignia, 1984-1985 (Box OS 7)
    - Tricentennial Key Rings (2), 1984-1985 (Box OS 7)
    - Tricentennial Mayors Cup Flag (20x14), 1984-1985 (Box OS 7)
    - Tricentennial Parade Banner (3x23), 1984-1985 (Box OS 7)
    - Tricentennial Banner (35-x30), 1984-1985 (Box OS 7)
    - Tricentennial T-Shirt, 1984-1985 (Box OS 7)
    - Tricentennial Mug, 1984-1985 (Box 95)
    - Tricentennial canvas bag printed with "Mayor Jim Dyer, Danbury, Connecticut 1684-1984, 300 Years as a Community" (Box OS 7)
    - Tricentennial "View of Danbury, Conn. 314 Piece Picture Puzzle", 1984-1985 (Box OS 4)
    - Tricentennial Red Felt Hat, 1984-1985 (Item 5)
    - The ungovernable city: the politics of urban problems and policy making by Douglas Yates, 1984 (Box 90)
    - Urban Planning, 1984-1986 (Box 69, Folder 1-2)
    - Budget Notes, 1985-1986 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Campaign 1985 (ALS Gov. O'Neill, T. Moffett) (Box 69, Folder 3-5)
    - Case Work (Peter Glaser and Jackie ?/Internal) Includes 4 polaroid color photographs, 1985 (Box 69, Folder 6-8)
    - Charles Ives and the Sounds of America (booklet), ca.1985 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Common Council Confirmation of Appointments, 1985 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Common Council Meeting Agenda and Minutes, October-November 1985 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Communications: Media-PR, Speech Preparation, 1985 (Box 69, Folder 11-13)
    - Correspondence (incoming) ALS Bill Ratchford, J. Rowland, J. Lieberman, C. Dodd, T. Moffett, 1985 (Box 69, Folder 14-15)
    - Correspondence (incoming/outgoing) ALS Gov. O'Neill, C. Dodd, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 1-8)
    - Correspondence, General (incoming), 1985 (Box 70, Folder 9-14)